Akinloye Bankole

Oba Abimbola street, Agodi, Ibadan, Oyo State Phone: 07062267403 Email: bankoleakinloye@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE:

A technical individual with experience in solar energy, rectifiers, inverters, power protective devices and technical services expertise to small and medium scale companies. I'm also an analytical individual with passion for technical designs and innovation.

PERSONAL DATA:

Marital Status: Single Nationality: Nigerian

Sex: Male

EDUCATION:

Lead City University, Ibadan 2019 - 2020

Diploma in Computer Science

Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo 2013 – 2017

Physics with Electronics

Lead City High School, Ibadan 2009 - 2013

Senior Secondary School Leaving Certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Olofa Middle/High School; Osogbo, Osun State

Jan, 2018 – Jan, 2019

NYSC

Post: Teacher

- Maintained good relationship between students and permanent staff of the school
- Establish Student and Teacher relationship in school.
- Established a debate competition every Wednesday.
- Being a Government owned establishment, I maintained act of discipline among students.
- Established a rule of NO NATIVE LANGUAGE SPEAKING (Yoruba) among students during school hours.

Solar World Apr, 2016 - Sept, 2016

Post: Field Engineer Intern

- Installation and maintenance of inverters.
- Solar energy generator engineering, operations, installation and maintenance.
- Implement solar installation project, install roof railing and stand offs, properly flash all roof penetrations string configuration for solar array, and run electrical D.C wires to inverters, charge

controllers and batteries.

- Provide pre-sales and post-sales technical support to customers including survey, commissioning, testing and maintenance.
- Installation of solar street lighting and solar powered boreholes.

I enjoy researching, playing board games and reading novels.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS:	
Autocad Certified Professional	2015
TRAINING:	
Startdotng (Beginner Software Development Training)	2019
AutoCad Professional Training, New Horizons, Ibadan.	2015
PERSONAL SKILLS:	
Efficient use of Microsoft Word and PowerPoint.	
Excellent written and oral communication skill.	
I have knowledge on HTML and CSS	
INTERESTS:	

REFEREES:

Dr Christopher Olowookere

Dr Paul Amalu.